[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Who was screaming there, Robert?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "That's my brother.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Natalie Jackson, what did you make of the interview I conducted with Robert Zimmerman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, I thought it was more of the same that we've seen.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Natalie Jackson", "Robert Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "I mean -- do you believe that the family is conspiring to create a version of events best suited to a defense under the \"Stand Your Ground\" law in Florida?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "JJS", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Does he have injuries now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "His nose is still broken.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "It's still broken?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "His nose is still broken, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Look, I'm not a doctor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "How do you explain that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "We're confident the medical records are going to explain all of George's medical history.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "What are you talking habit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Toure, calm down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman", "George"]}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "And are you abreast of more information than anybody else in America right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "One thing I notice is obviously the Zimmerman family is banding together to try to keep George out of jail for the rest of his life.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Are you aware of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "That's not the information that I had 30 minutes ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "That's a pretty serious responsible piece of journalism, isn't it, Toure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "In the first days, in the first weeks of the situation, what many people were doing, what I was trying to do in that was to pile on and to say, hey, look, this guy is not doing the right thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "What don't I understand about America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "You're showing you clearly don't understand the depth of the pain in the American soul that is at play in this situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Do you believe that George Zimmerman murdered Trayvon Martin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "You've convicted him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "You asked me what I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "How can they justify that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I don't know how they justify it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Would that be OK for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "EINSTEIN: A PG-13 would be 100 percent what we're looking for.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "What is the message that you're really sending with this movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Well, I think it taps into something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Where is that line, do you think, to be drawn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "When you she this movie and you see these kids beating each other up, or these kids coming against somebody for there being black, or they don't look the way they're supposed to, or they are gay, or whatever reason, and they get mercilessly beaten up, that's where you draw the line.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Are you a changed character, as a leopard changes spots, Harvey?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Listen, I never bullied anybody in my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harvey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "How many times have you done this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "This will be my 14th time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kitty Wells"]}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Is that who you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "CENTIRE: Well, Kitty Wells was queen of country music forever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "But are you the current queen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "If they say they about me, I'll sure take that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Kiowa.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "How do I pronounce that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Just like you did it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Is it where -- one of those guys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "WRB", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Because it is a special world, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "It's the people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Is it part of the territory, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "I just want to ask you what effect that had on your life afterwards, how it changed your outlook on life, to lose so many people that you were so close to in one horrible day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Horrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "A cliched thing to say, but it's often true, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "It is very true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "Second time around better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "CENTIRE: Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "What did you learn, A, about you as a wife, and B, about the kind of husband that best suited you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "The thing I learned about me is that I need to communicate more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Oh yes, no talk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Three days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Yes, I could go three days sulking up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "To be a successful wife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Is there much call for country music in Malibu?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Oh, yeah, everywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Malibu"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Will you be singing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]